cedcommerce.com 2019-12-29

# Privacy Policy Page - CedCommerce Inc

## Purpose

CedCommerce an ecommerce wing of CedCoss Technologies Pvt Ltd , 3/460 Vishwas Khand Gomti Nagar Lucknow India respects the privacy of its clients and the website visitors. This Privacy Policy has been created to make you aware of what information we may collect from you and how you shared information is being used from all our site ( <https://cedcommerce.com/>), subdomains and any of the social media pages. You can also visit our [customer service page](https://cedcommerce.com/customer-service) and check all our terms and conditions.

  * <https://www.facebook.com/cedcommerce>
  * <https://twitter.com/cedcommerce>
  * <https://www.linkedin.com/company/cedcommerce>

We do our every bit do protect customer information and from time to time make changes to the privacy policy which through a notification is being displayed on the website. Regular visitors are aware of this things and for everyone going through the website make sure to go through the privacy policy page before sharing any information. The website is accessible through multiple devices and this privacy policy applies to all such access.

## What Information Do We Collect ?

Any information that you share while processing any order on the website, website page visits such as payment information, shipping information, products you showed interest and personal information like name, address, email address, mobile number with a verification call, which page you visited, Skype Details, products purchased, how do you came to know about us, source of shipping will be collected by us. We may use these information to contact you to provide suitable information. Password related information is stored in a one-way encrypted format. We will also collect details such as FTP,  API details & Server/ WebSite details for development purposes as well as to provide good support. Once the work is complete or for any other reason, it is your responsibility that you change the credentials. When you are providing information you fill a terms and condition and only after that those information reaches to us. As a backend administrator we will able to have an access of your backend as long as you stay as our customer whereby we will able to access your profile and make the necessary changes.Time to time we make changes to the policy so you should regularly revisit to be aware of such changes. We will, however, notify about such changes by notification at the top of the website. We will also store information such as Browser Information, IP address, operating system, location, date and automatically store the same. We don’t collect personal information from children under age of 13 and also, they should not use the website.

## Use of Information

We will use the information that is being gathered from you for the following ways :

  * Order and Transaction Related Information.
  * Sending Associated Product Emails based on the interest shows.
  * Sending New Product Information.
  * Product Related and Major Updates.
  * Improving the overall structure of site to give personalized experience based personal traits.
  * Conduct surveys, promotions and marketing.
  * Payment Related Telephonic Conversations.
  * Feedback related Mails and Calls.
  * Informational Mails and Calls.
  * Industry related news and updates.
  * Scheduled Calling.
  * Service Related Mails.
  * Notification Mails.
  * Text Messaging Service.
.

There is always a procedure for unsubscription to receiving such email and newsletters after you won’t be receiving such information.

## How do we deal with 3rd Parties?

Any associated affiliate for may receive the personal information shared and they may contact you on for offering there solution and services. Associated partners will receive the necessary information of the clients in order to reach out to them to offer the complete service solution. We follow the strict policy of non sharing of data with 3rd Parties or making it public.  We don’t allow any 3rd parties to conduct contest and surveys and even if we do then we may prohibit them from using the information for any other purpose. In the event of the sale of business, all the information would be transferred but before that information would be shared with you related to the same. We may conducts advertisements and use third party tool and share information including name, adress, email address , telephone number to show tailored based advertisements of product that may suit your purpose. We reserve the right to disclose your personal information as required by law, and as necessary to protect the property, interests and rights of CedCommerce and the CedCommerce Affiliates. The CedCommerce website might contain links to the 3rd Parties Websites. Those 3rd Party Website may use cookies in order to gather information . This privacy policy does not cover their privacy setup. So we suggest to go through each site privacy policy separately. We will use third party software like MailChimp, Hot Jar, Live Chat Facilitators, Google Analytics and Google Adwords to track the visits of the prospects and for remarketing and retargeting purpose.

## Choice to Opt In / Opt Out

We want our voice reaches only to those who really want to listen. In case you don’t want to listen to us we have provided a way you can always reach us to at **admin@cedcommerce.com** and we would stop all communication with you. You could also mail In case you don’t want any service related mail or want your account deleted which you have with us or want all type of communication stopped with us.

At any time the client can opt out of any service by removing the software and can also delete / change any information which he has provided earlier.

You could also call us at - (+91) -7234976892 or toll-free number at : 888-882-0953 (FOR USA) . At any time the client can opt out of any service by removing the software and can also delete / change any information which he has provided earlier.

You could also unsubscribe to the email services of CedCommerce by clicking on the unsubscription link provided at the bottom of the email.

## What are Cookies and What Information does it gathers ?

Cookies are small piece if information that is transferred to your computer as soon as you visit a website. We use traffic log cookies for statistical analysis in order to tailor it your needs. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate our Website and Services, while others are used to enable a faster log -in process. Once the purpose is achieved, the required data is immediately removed from our system. In fact, cookies further our objective to allow you take complete advantage of our site. You can always change your setting whereby you will be notified whenever a site is using cookies and it will depend on your acceptance whether information is transferred or not. Cookies used by affiliates and partners are not covered under this privacy policy.

There are various types of cookie:

  * Strictly necessary cookies : 

These are cookies that are required for the operation of our Website. They include, for example, cookies that enable users to log into secure areas of our Website.

  * Analytical/performance cookies : 

These types of cookies allow us to recognize, count the number of visitors, and see how visitors move around our Website when they are using it. This assists us to improve the way in which our Website works, for example, by ensuring that you can find what you are looking for easily.

  * Functionality cookies : 

These cookies are used to recognize you when you return to our Website. They enable the personalization of content, recognition of users, and also remember your user preferences (for example, your choice of language or region).

  * Session Cookies : 

Session cookies exist only during an online session. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser or turn off your computer. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely id entify you during a session or while you are logged into the Website or Services. This allows us to process your online transactions and requests and verify your identity, after you have logged in, as you move through our Website or Services.

## Updation in Personal Information / Inquiries / Complaints

In case you want any changes in the information you could mail us at **admin@cedcommerce.com** . Alternatively you could write us at :

CedCommerce Inc,

3/460 Vishwas Khand,

Gomti Nagar,

Lucknow - 226010

## Security & Term of Information

There is no fixed term or duration where we will be keeping the information. We may keep as long as it is required for the purpose mentioned in the policy and as governed by the Law. CedCommerce.com in encrypted form using industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) connections to help protect such information from interception.
